



# **Luiz Miguel Silva Lima**

**Date of birth:** 03/01/2000 | **Phone number:** (+351) 925002615 (Mobile) |

Email address: miguelsl2000@gmail.com | Website: www.silvalima.dev |

**LinkedIn:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/miguelsilvalima/ | **GitHub:** 

https://github.com/Aeziren

Address: 2490-126, Ourém (Willing to Relocate), Portugal (Home)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a Freelancer Software Developer with a strong foundation in Python and experience in back end tools such as Django, Flask and SQL. Also, I am well-versed in software engineering tools and methodologies such as Docker, Git, CI/CD, Agile and RESTful APIs. Additionally, I have solid knowledge in Cybersecurity and practical experience with the deployment and management of applications in cloud environments.

Due to my long-standing passion for the technology field and my professional background, I am confident in my ability to quickly adapt to any work environment and acquire the necessary skills to meet the specific demands of a project.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - CURRENT Remote

#### **BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER SELF-EMPLOYED**

- Python
- Django
- lavascript
- RESTful API
- SQL
- Google Cloud Platform
- Git
- CI/CD

2016 - 2021 Rio das Ostras, Brazil

## **COMPUTER MAINTENANCE SELF-EMPLOYED**

- Problem Solving
- Analytical Skills
- Hardware Knowledge
- Verbal Skills
- Continuous Learning
- Responsibility
- Self-Taught
- Logical Thinking

01/2022 - 12/2022 Batalha, Portugal

## FACTORY OPERATOR MATCERÂMICA

- Time Management
- Teamwork
- Coordination
- Effective Communication
- Practical Thinking
- Quality Assurance

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2022 - CURRENT Remote, Brazil

**BACHELOR'S DEGREE, SOFTWARE ENGINEERING UNOPAR University** 

2019 - 2022 Rio das Ostras, Brazil

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY, SYSTEM ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT UNOPAR University

2016 - 2017 Rio das Ostras, Brazil

**ASSEMBLY AND MAINTENANCE OF COMPUTERS AND CELLPHONES** Prepara Cursos

2023 Remote

**JUNIOR CYBERSECURITY ANALIST Cisco** 

## DIGITAL SKILLS

Python | Django | JavaScript | C | Unit Testing | Flask | RESTful api | SQL | Linux | CSS | HTML | CI/CD | Docker | Agile | Git | Bootstrap | Databases | Cybersecurity | Object-Oriented | Programming | Cloud Computing (GCP) | RegEx

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PORTUGUESE** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C1	C1	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

### **PROJECTS**

**Social Network Website** This site implement a RESTful API built using Django and use AJAX to interact with it. In this site you can register, modify your profile, create posts, follow other users and like their posts!

Links <a href="https://youtu.be/SnUs5O5cdOQ">https://github.com/Aeziren/social-network</a>

**E-commerce Website** Marketplace website made using Django. Users can register, create their listings, and place bids and comments on other users listings.

Links https://youtu.be/vb9f6I0mcgl | https://github.com/Aeziren/e-commerce

**Backup App** Assign any folder in your system and this application will keep track of all changes on it and made a backup copy in a directory of your choice. All changes made will get logged in .txt file and in the console.

Links <a href="https://youtu.be/769DdzG\_GBw">https://github.com/Aeziren/folder-mirror</a>

**Email Website** A single page application where everything happens without the need to reload the page. Users can register, log in, navigate through their emails and send emails to other users.

Links <a href="https://youtu.be/93RYSu-Kvbs">https://youtu.be/93RYSu-Kvbs</a> | <a href="https://github.com/Aeziren/email">https://github.com/Aeziren/email</a>

#### **DRIVING LICENCE**

**Driving Licence:** A **Driving Licence:** B